{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Curtain Repair \u0026 Alteration Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","__cache./api/resource/task/40169/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40169,"taskName":"Drapes or Curtains - Repair or Alter","taskDescription":"Custom Sew or Alter Drapes or Curtains","xmTaskDescriptor":"Curtain Repair \u0026 Alteration Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":275,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Drapes Alter window board drapery","textMessagingName":"Repair Drapes","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically handled by decorators, specialty firms or drycleaner-linked alteration services.","rolloverShortDesc":"Convert fabric to drapes or alter existing drapes.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Custom Sew or Alter Drapes or Curtains.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Curtain Repair \u0026 Alterations \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Alter Drapes \u0026 Curtains","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":24,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Window Coverings or Curtains Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Drapes or Curtains - Repair or Alter","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Drapes and Curtain Project","urlName":"Drapes-or-Curtains-Repair-or-Alter","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Curtain Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs, Reviews","searchKeywords":"drapes, drapery, draperies, curtains, window coverings, window, coverings, window treaments","emcCategoryOid":-12079,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":479,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40169/":{"taskOID":40169,"originalTaskOID":40169,"setID":479,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1357,"questionDisplayText":"Repair needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"List any repair you need for your drapes.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5372,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rod or frame pulling out of wall","answerDisplayText":"Rod or frame pulling out of wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1131,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Broken rod or frame","answerDisplayText":"Broken rod or frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1817,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Damaged shutter slat","answerDisplayText":"Damaged shutter slat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1809,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Damaged blind slat","answerDisplayText":"Damaged blind slat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1815,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Damaged pulley system","answerDisplayText":"Damaged pulley system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1812,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Damaged fashion fabric","answerDisplayText":"Damaged fashion fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1814,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Damaged lining fabric","answerDisplayText":"Damaged lining fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1357,"questionDisplayText":"Repair needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"List any repair you need for your drapes.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5372,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rod or frame pulling out of wall","answerDisplayText":"Rod or frame pulling out of wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1131,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Broken rod or frame","answerDisplayText":"Broken rod or frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1817,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Damaged shutter slat","answerDisplayText":"Damaged shutter slat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1809,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Damaged blind slat","answerDisplayText":"Damaged blind slat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1815,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Damaged pulley system","answerDisplayText":"Damaged pulley system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1812,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Damaged fashion fabric","answerDisplayText":"Damaged fashion fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1814,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Damaged lining fabric","answerDisplayText":"Damaged lining fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5372,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Rod or frame pulling out of wall","answerDisplayText":"Rod or frame pulling out of wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1131,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Broken rod or frame","answerDisplayText":"Broken rod or frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1817,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Damaged shutter slat","answerDisplayText":"Damaged shutter slat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1809,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Damaged blind slat","answerDisplayText":"Damaged blind slat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1815,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Damaged pulley system","answerDisplayText":"Damaged pulley system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1812,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Damaged fashion fabric","answerDisplayText":"Damaged fashion fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1814,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Damaged lining fabric","answerDisplayText":"Damaged lining fabric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}